<resources>

    <!-- General:  -->

    <string name="app_name">OHDM Offline Viewer</string>
    <string name="OHDM">Open Historical Data Map</string>


    <!-- About Activity Strings:  -->

    <string name="about_ohdm_offline_viewer">
        .. was developed in 2019 by students during a course by Mr. Schwotzer. It shall serve as a prototype to display maps stored in OHDM for the first time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_ohdm">
        .. stores annual Open Street Map (OSM) maps.
        This makes it the first system that can process historical maps.
        OHDM was founded in 2016 under the leadership of Prof. Schwotzer at the Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft in Berlin.
        Since then, numerous final theses and Open Source projects have been created on an OHDM basis.
    </string>
    <string name="find_us">
        find us here
    </string>


    <!-- Home Activity Strings:  -->

    <string name="home_usage">
        To view your own maps, simply move them to your mobile phone in the "OHDM" folder.
        Otherwise, you can view and download available maps in the "Maps" tab.
    </string>

    <string name="save_map_button">
        Save and Navigate
    </string>

    <string name="current_map">
        current map:
    </string>


    <!-- FragmentOptions Strings:  -->

    <string name="dark_mode">
        Enable or Disable the Darkmode
    </string>

    <string name="permission_access_location">
        Allow OHDM to access you location
    </string>

    <string name="permission_access_location_further_info">
        We dont safe or use any of your private data!
    </string>

    <string name="permission_write_local_storage">
        Allow us to write into your devise storage
    </string>

    <string name="permission_write_local_storage_further_info">
        We need this to safe maps onto your local device
    </string>

    <string name="request_map_info">
        Here you can request Maps which you haven found in the existing maps.
        The Map will then be created by our Server and show up in the available maps.
        (for you and everyone else).
    </string>


    <!-- FragmentRequestNewMap Strings:  -->

    <string name="name">enter a name</string>
    <string name="long_max">Long. max</string>
    <string name="lat_max">Lat. max</string>
    <string name="long_min">Long. min </string>
    <string name="lat_min">Lat. min</string>
    <string name="coords_info">Enter latitude and longitude</string>
    <string name="submit_request">submit request</string>


    <!-- Toolbar Menu  Strings:  -->

    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_faq">FAQ</string>


    <!-- FragmentRequestStatus Strings:  -->

    <string name="status_info_done">The server has processed your request successfully. You can now download the map in the download Tab</string>
    <string name="status_info_error"> A problem occurred while the server processed your request -- we are sorry </string>
    <string name="status_info_downloading"> The server is downloading the data you requested from our database </string>
    <string name="status_info_converting"> The server has successfully retrieved all the data from the database. Now he builds a map from them </string>
    <string name="status_info_requesting"> Your request was successfully submitted to the server </string>
</resources>
